Resume

Table of content

- 1. General Info
- 2. Contacts
- 3. Desired Position
- 4. Work Experience
 - 1. April 2019 May 2022
 - 2. May 2022 April 2023
 - 3. May 2023 July 2023
- 5. About me

Some pdf readers don't provide access to use a links

General Info

Name: Kurkurin Nikita

Gender: Male (He)

Age: 22 years (born on 23 March 2001)

Languages:

Primary: Ukrainian/Russian

Secondary (speaking + listening + reading): English

Education:

Incomplete higher technical education in University on Software Engineer specialization (4 years)

General Experience of Programming: 4 years (begin from May 2019)

Technologies I worked with

- Programming languages: Python (4 years, primary language), JavaScript (without frameworks 3 years),
 Swift (one pet project), Kotlin (one pet project), c# (few pet projects, learn sometimes unity);
- Frameworks / Big Libraries: Django, Django Rest
 Framework, Fast Api, Flask, Dependency Injector,
 SQLAlchemy, PeeWee, PyQT5, PySide6, Kivy,
 Pytest, Unittest, Pygame, Unity and other libraries
 which give access to some service, wrote myself libraries
 for a few services;
- Databases:

- SQL: PostgreSQL, MySQL, MariaDB, Oracle,
 Percona, SQLite;
- NoSQL: MongoDB, Redis;
- Tests: Work with TDD methodology, know about test types and cover my code with tests, on python I use pytest and sometimes unittest, but last time usually it's pytest;
- Protocols: http, https, tcp, upd, ftp, sftp, ssh, smtp, pop3, imap, vnc, xmpp, write a api for work with it and use a api for work with it;
- Operating systems: Linux, Windows, MacOS,
 Android, IOS, HarmonyOS, on all of this systems I was a minimum a two years;
- Containerization and deployment: docker, dockercompose, linux;
- Version Control Systems: git, github, gitlab, bitbucket;
- Data exchange formats: json, xml, csv, xls, xlsx, pdf and others;
- Documentation: I make a documentation for my code, from usually comments to doc frameworks like sphinx
- **Soft skills**: work with orders (start from freelance), know develop flow, from technical task to deploy project on server, work as alone, as team member, work with different methodologies like scrum, kanban

Contacts

Phone number: +48 451 681 146

E-Mail:

Primary: <u>kurkurin2001@gmail.com</u>

Secondary: <u>collabortiss@outlook.com</u>

Another links:

Telegram: @moonvent (http://t.me/moonvent)

Instagram: @murbenchik

(<u>https://www.instagram.com/murbenchik/</u>)

Github: https://github.com/moonvent

You can call or write on any of this socials, I'm always online

Desired Position

Python Developer (Middle)

Specializations:

- Software Engineer
- Programmer, developer
- System administrator
- Tester

Employment:

- full time
- part time
- project work

Work schedule:

- full day
- shift schedule
- flexible schedule
- remote working

Work experience

April 2019 - May 2022

Tags:

- IT, System Integration, Internet
- Internet Company (Search Engines, Payment Systems, Social Networks, Information and Educational, Entertainment Resources, Website Promotion etc.)
- Software Development
- System Integration, Technological and Business Processes Automation, IT Consulting

Start my work in 18 years, begin from freelance, work on different freelance marketplaces, usually work on Ukraine marketplaces, and begin from different easy job, parsers, scrappers, bots, and other little soft, for example server script or desktop application for cross-platform.

A little late, from a 2021 year I start to work with more harder projects. Mainly, it was web development, but I also worked on writing software for the desktop and continued to work on small projects to entertain myself with something.

On all my work experience on freelance I get throught all cycle of order, from searching projects, create a technical task, speak with orderer, make a architecture design, code the project, test it, and after that pass it to order, in all my experience I make a couple of hundred a little orders, and a

several dozens a middle and big project (work more then one week), know how to interact with orderers and how to solve the conflicts, work in a small teams and on outsource.

If summarize, I get from this period a much experience how to work with orders, project flow, how to learn new features, get new knowledges, and take a new target, understand what I need and what I'm interested in. In Jenuary I solve to start work in company cause I want new experience and work with more complex and sophisticated projects, and also increase a salary and general of my engineer level.

All technologies, which I touch in this period:

- python (primary language, but not fear a learn a new languages)
- js (basics)
- c# (at this moment learn it, cause I have a interest about Unity)
- html, css
- sql
- mysql, postgresql, oracle, sqlite
- telegram api
- work with web (parsers) with requests, aiohttp
- flask, fastapi, django + django rest framework
- tkinter, kivy, pyqt
- nosql
- mongo, redis
- docker, nginx, linux (debian, centos)

- protocols, http, websockets, udp, tcp, ftp, sftp and others
- git, github, gitlab, bitbucket
- unittest, pytest
- work with different api, crypto marketplace, work with fileformats like xlsx, pdf and other
- learn an algorithms, OOP principles
- a little experience a mobile developing
- and more else, but at this moment I can't remember more

May 2022 - April 2023

I get a job in two company, after a one month I chose one and work it almost a one year, that was a project-based work, and I'm work with foreign clients (before that, work only in my country orderers), and strengthened skills in desktop programming (pyqt) and up skills in web development (django with django-rest-framework), I learned about new programming methodologies, started covering code with tests and documenting all the code I wrote. I also improved my coding skills, put into practice many design patterns, and simply became better at writing code, technologies which I up:

- pyqt5 and pyside6
- english language (not my primary language)
- django, django rest framework, fast api, and generally rest api concept
- sql databases, exactly mariadb, and postgresql
- cache, redis and celery
- docker and devops features, as like linux, setup the nginx, work with cron, and other a little features of development and deployment projects
- use test as usually features and add docs to projects

Cause it was a project work, and often I a two - three month work and one - two a rest, I chose work with more stable

companies that have a steady workload, and solve to find a new work.

Company site: http://smartnlg.com/

May 2023 - July 2023

I got a job in new company, here I work with a old tech stack (python, fastapi, mongo, postgre), but get more experience with work of a legacy and not a good condition (softly) code, work with agile technology (scrum) and constantly a team, make a code review, and take part in team building, brainstorms and summarize, up not only a hard skills but and soft skills. In this period I consolidated this skills:

- soft skills:
 - patience
 - discussions with the team
 - brainstorming sessions
 - conversations
 - dialogues with colleagues
- hard skills:
 - increase a OOP principle to work with code
 - better documentation code
 - better test code
 - work with nosql database (mongo and redis)
 - work with full async code

And solidify a agile workflow, in this company we try to work with different workflow, start from kanban and switch to scrum and try to configurate a use of story points.

I worked on a project that attracts people and serves as a platform for providing various banking services, be it credit, deferment, mortgage, or just a loan. I worked with the APIs of different banks and implemented new services into the system, wrote various services for working with bank APIs and not only with bank APIs, was involved in service design and development of services for authorization, authentication, mailing, and similar services, as well as adding new integrations to the system.

Company site: https://x-lab.com.ru/

If summarize all of this, I can't describe in all details all my experience on this pages, we can speak about experience more detail on interview and not only about experience.

About me

22 years old was born in Ukraine and in 21 year of my life relocate to Republic of Poland, I like the Warsaw (I live here a half of year) and like a nature (live nearby a small forest). From my childhood I like to learn something from techincs like computers, consoles, learn how it work on hardware and more like how it's work on software level, and from this I try a few directions and chose the programming and near industry, I like to follow a new techs in different sectors, pc, laptops, mobiles, cars, all which have a anything that has a circuit board and transistors with a binary signal. Also I like a culture of different countries, songs, cinema, books, videogames, I count that last it's a next level of art, which contain all types of oldest art, like books, cinema, music, and another. I like a national culture of every countries, and In particular, architecture attracts me more towards Western European architecture, narrow streets, quiet people, and the architecture of the Silver or Golden Age. I don't have a bad habits like smoking, drinking, use the drags, don't eat a sugar not drink a coffee, I follow a proper diet and do stretching exercises (if I work remotely) every couple of hours because work is mostly sedentary.

My life and career goals involve creating products which need to customers, or product which can improve anything in this world, this can be a little or not thing, but if this thing will be need it for least one person and will be useful for this person, I will be happy that I helped this person to save time or do something with some pleasure, then if he did it without this product.